Reid Naaykens

Junior Web Developer | Please visit reidnaa.github.io

103-391 Tyee rd Victoria B.C. | 204-997-7024 | reidnaaykens@gmail.com

github.com/reidnaa in linkedin.com/in/reid-naaykens-527135b8/

Summary

I am a junior web developer that is looking for an opportunity to continue to learn while contributing to a modern development team. I spent just under 3 years honing my skills as a Technical Support Specialist where I picked up the front end chops I used to transition to my current role in development. Having spent the better part of a year now in a pure development position I am excited to keep learning and bring my steadfast determination and personality to a new role. I am looking for an opportunity to build upon the strong foundation that I have worked hard to acquire and am eager to keep learning.

Skills

FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES: SASS, Bootstrap, ¡Query, ReactJS

PLATFORMS: Shopify, Bigcommerce, Jira, Github, Bitbucket, Jira, Wordpress, Drupal

PROGRAMS: Photoshop, Illustrator, Premier, Sublime 3, PHPstorm, GIT, SVN, Gulp, Grunt

LANGUAGES: Responsive CSS, Javascript, HTML, PHP, Twig, Liquid

Education

Web Development Bootcamp 2017 Graduate

Oct - Dec 2017

Lighthouse Labs

Eight week intensive bootcamp in web developing

Work experience

Web Developer

2018 - 2019

Verb Interactive

- Receive daily tasks on a variety of site using Jira and Redmine
- Pull down, push up repos using GIT (GItlab) or SVN
- Build development sites for testing code changes
- Build new features for sites
- Update existing features for legacy sites
- Communicate with the Account Managers with specifics of each task

Web Support Specialist

2015 - 2018

Pixel Union Design Ltd.

- Identify, fix and log theme bugs in bitbucket and Github
- Recognizing areas of improvement within themes and apps to improve our products and support our customers.
- Provide technical support to merchants helping to identify issues and solve them
- Making customizations based on the customers needs with JS, jQuery, CSS/SCSS, Liquid and HTML
- Continuously learning to implement custom styles and functions

Volunteering

Surfrider Vancouver Island · Volunteer Coordinator

Make sure volunteers get gloves, sign waver, and inform any other information one would need for safety and regulations for the day

Travel to a different beach every month on Vancouver Island to collect trash that accumulates from marine wash up and beach goers

vancouverisland.surfrider.org/

Discover Techtoria · Event Support

General support, counting patrons and then clean up for the event

one of the only events where locals and visitors come together to discover the innovation that's stemming from right here in Victoria. Attendees get to interact with the people and their creations to better understand who and what is driving Victoria's largest industry

https://www.viatec.ca/events/discovertectoria-2018

Viatech Fuck-up Night · Event Support

General set up and support then clean up for the event

F*ckUp Nights is a global movement where stories of failed businesses and projects are told, questioned and celebrated. It started in 2012 in Mexico City.

https://www.facebook.com/fupnightsvictoria/

MS Society of Canada MS Walk 2018-2019 · Event Support

General set up and support and take down for the event